CONTACT ME

Newmarket, ON - Canada 437-972-2174 rlevenhagen@gmail.com www.ricardowebdev.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML
CSS
JavaScript
React
GitHub
FireBase
Adobe Creative Suite:
Photoshop | InDesign

EDUCATION

Web Developer Boot camp Juno College of Technology | 2021/2022

Introduction to JavaScript
Juno College of Technology | 2021

Introduction to HTML and CSS Juno College of Technology | 2021

University Gama Filho (Brazil) Bachelor's degree in Physiotherapy

SOCIAL

github.com/rilevenhagen

linkedin.com/in/ricardo-levenhagen

twitter.com/Levenhagen

RICARDO LEVENHAGEN

Front-End Web Developer

ABOUT

I'm a Front End Web Developer, who loves what I do. I have a strong 10+ years' combined foundation in production management, leadership and customer service across 3 different continents. My diverse education and background equips me with adaptable skills and knowledge in order serve clients in the best possible way and make delivering projects with a team smooth and organized.

PROJECT

Project Binge Fest | bingefest.netlify.app | 2022

In this group programming project, we were tasked with completing a site that
provides a TV show or movie to watch and a restaurant to order takeout,
according to user input of location and preferences. Tools used: HTML, CSS,
React, RESTFul API, Firebase, Github

Project Cryptocurrency Search | cryptocurrencysearch.netlify.app | 2022

 This React project made a request to the two Cryptocurrency APIs, where one is based on user input in a search bar and the other returned image, description, and news about Cryptocurrency displayed on the page. Tools used: HTML, React, RESTful API, Github

Project Willow | willowsjourney.netlify.app | 2021

 PSD Conversion where I created a three-page website. Tools used: HTML, CSS, Github

WORK EXPERIENCE

PRINT PARTNER INC. | 2018 - 2021 Production Manager | 2020-2021

- Promoted to manager, led a team of 10 employees, ran production smoothly as possible meeting delivery deadlines of products
- Purchased and organized inventory for 7 printers and the company's entire inventory that could reach \$50,000 per month.

Print and photoshop technician | 2018-2020

• Prepare, review and sent all images for printing and shipping

PHOTOGRAPHER AT STUDIO RICARDO LEVENHAGEN 2008/2018 Owner and photographer

• Owner of the studio where I was responsible for closing the contract and the entire process from the sale of the photographic package to delivery to the client. Working in the field of event photography and studio photography.

HOSPITALITY IN BARCELONA (ES) & LONDON (UK)

- Server, Hotel H10 in Barcelona | 2007 2008
- Second Manager, Yosushi in London | 2006 2007
- Server, Silvo's Coffee Shop | 2005 2006

Additional Experience

• Owner of physical therapy office - treated patients and assisted in their recovery